Guide to the James Otey Bradford Papers, 1869-1919
Department of Special Collections
James Otey Bradford Papers,
1869-1919
Special Collections M046
James Otey Bradford
2 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions:
None.
Provenance:
Gift of Harriet Bradford, 1919.
BIOGRAPHY
James Otey Bradford (d 1919?] was born in Virginia and served as a lieutenant in the Confederate Navy. After the war he worked for various English shipping lines. He began his employ with Wells, Fargo in New York City. In this position he was in charge of freight and travel requests for tourists. He left Wells, Fargo and moved to San Francisco where he was employed by the Palace Hotel. He shortly returned to the employ of Wells, Fargo and remained with them until retirement. In his later years he served as the director of the Wells, Fargo historical exhibit at the Columbian Exhibition of 1893. Later he was placed in charge of all Wells, Fargo historical exhibits. He retired after forty years service with the company. Much of the present collection represents Mr. Bradford's interest in the history of Wells, Fargo.
SCOPE AND CONTENT
The Bradford papers contain James Otey Bradford's correspondence from 1888-1919. Much of it is correspondence pertaining to his duties with the Wells, Fargo & Co. There are also typescripts of historical writings (possibly copied from printed sources) and copies of newspaper articles pertaining to the early days of stage coaching, the men involved and the crimes committed against stages. Biographical material pertaining to stage robbers, as well as drivers are in the collection.
An important part of the collection are the numerous pictures of employees of Wells, Fargo and the coaches, as well as pictures of sailing vessels and related transportation media.
The papers of Henry Chester Ward, an early employee of the company are included in the collection. Among Ward's papers are his diary for a short period of 1869-1870.
SERIES DESCRIPTION
- Correspondence (Boxes 1-2)
  Letters of J.O. Bradford arranged chronologically; 1888-1901. Letter to J. 0. Bradford arranged alphabetically by signer and chronologically under each signer, 1888-1919.
- Manuscript Material (Box 3)
  Wells, Fargo manuscripts. Typescripts of articles and unpublished reports, biographical sketches and reminiscences. Articles and poems probably by Bradford.
- Miscellany (Box 4)
  Memorabilia and personal papers of J. 0. Bradford.
- Photographs (Box 4)
  Photographs of the men and equipment of Wells, Fargo.
- Henry Chester Ward Papers (Box 4)
  Correspondence, diary, and last will and testament.
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence
  - Out-going 1888-1899 (Box 1., Volume 1)
  - Out-going 1892-1899 (Box 1., Volume 2)
  - Out-going 1893-1897 (Box 1., Volume 3)
  - Out-going 1896-1901 (Box 1., Volume 4)
    (A listing of the names to whom letters were sent has been prepared and placed in the front of books 1-4).
  - Incoming 1898-1902 (Box 2., Folder 5)
  - Incoming 1887-1919 (Box 2., Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook of papers relating to Bradford's employment and achievements. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Letters A-B (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Letters C (Box 2., Folder 9)
  - Letters D-G (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Letters H (Box 2., Folder 11)
  - Letters J-M (Box 2., Folder 12)
  - Letters 0 (Box 2., Folder 13)
  - Letters S (Box 2., Folder 14)
  - Letters T-V (Box 2., Folder 15)
  - Letters W-Z (Box 2., Folder 16)
  - Letters about Bradford, 1892-1900 (Box 2., Folder 17)
  - Wells, Fargo Express Directory, 1880. (Box 2., Folder 17a)
- Manuscript material
  - Wells, Fargo account book, n.d. (Box 3., Folder 18)
  - Memorandum book of [Golden Gate] Park Museum display. Memorandum book with notes about early express companies and mining communities. Catalogue... Wells, Fargo & Co., Historical Exhibit at the 1893 World's Columbian Exhibit. Catalogue of the Wells, Fargo exhibit at the Museum. Golden Gate Park. (Box 3., Folder 19)
  - Code Book. (Box 3., Folder 20)
  - Wells, Fargo business letters, mostly printed. (Box 3., Folder 21)
  - A. Lyman. Political letter to the editor of the National Democrat, March 9, 1891. (Box 3., Folder 22)
  - A pulpit for Ingersoll. (Box 3., Folder 23)
  - A Synopsis of status of Wells, Fargo to Aug. l, 1892. (Box 3., Folder 24)
  - A romance of the west. (Box 3., Folder 25)
  - Adams [Express] and Co. (Box 3., Folder 26)
  - Anti-Imperialist. (Box 3., Folder 27)
  - Between Treasure City, Nevada and Hamilton in 1869. (Box 3., Folder 28)
  - Billy Moore and the Simian. (Box 3., Folder 29)
  - Cleveland, Grover (Box 3., Folder 30)
  - Confederate cruiser Florida. (Box 3., Folder 31)
  - Early days of Wells, Fargo (Box 3., Folder 32)
  - Eugene Blair (Box 3., Folder 33)
  - Eugene Blair and Jimmy Brown (Box 3., Folder 34)
  - Fortino Viscayno and his raid upon Guymas, Mexico. (Box 3., Folder 35)
  - George Hackett (Box 3., Folder 36)
  - H.C. Ward and his flight from Treasure City to Hamilton, Nevada. (Box 3., Folder 37)
  - History of Wells, Fargo. (Box 3., Folder 38)
  - In Confederate days. (Box 3., Folder 39)
  - Jimmy Brown, an expressman's story. (Box 3., Folder 40)
  - Lowden's wild ride. (Box 3., Folder 41)
  - Memoirs of happy days. (Box 3., Folder 42)
  - Old pony the stage dog. (Box 3., Folder 43)
  - Pioneer Staging (Box 3., Folder 44)
  - Pony Express (Box 3., Folder 45)
  - Red the Owyhee stage dog. (Box 3., Folder 46)
  - Silent Tom of Flower Point. (Box 3., Folder 47)
  - Silent Tom of Flower Point.(2) (Box 3., Folder 48)
  - Slade, (Joseph Alfred] (Box 3., Folder 49)
  - Stage robbery (Box 3., Folder 50)
  - The killing of long-haired (Box 3., Folder 51)
  - The verdict. (Box 3., Folder 52)
  - Two historic men of Nevada. (Box 3., Folder 53)
  - John J. Valentine (Box 3., Folder 54)
  - Wells, Fargo and Co. express and banking. (Box 3., Folder 55)
  - Wells, Fargo & Co. from 1864-9. (Box 3., Folder 56)
  - W.H. "Shotgun" Taylor. (Box 3., Folder 57)
  - Untitled reminiscences (Box 3., Folder 58)
  - Poems (Box 3., Folder 59)
  - Poems (Box 3., Folder 60)
  - Excerpt from untitled article. (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Miscellany
  - Notes (Box 4., Folder 62)
  - Columbian Exposition (Box 4., Folder 63)
  - RR passes and cards. (Box 4., Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Box 4., Folder 65)
  - Dr. J.E. Monjaras, biographical (Box 4., Folder 66)
  - Memoranda (Box 4., Folder 67)
  - Notes from Palace Hotel. (Box 4., Folder 68)
  - Notes, unidentified. (Box 4., Folder 69)
  - Advertising (Box 4., Folder 70)
  - Pass container (Box 4., Folder 71)
  - Wells, Fargo advertising (Box 4., Folder 72)
  - Bradford stickers (Box 4., Folder 73)
  - Short biographical sketches (Box 4., Folder 74)
  - Pony Express stamps (Box 4., Folder 75)
  - Notice of reward (Box 4., Folder 76)
  - Change of insurance rate. (Box 4., Folder 77)
  - Admission day picnic (Box 4., Folder 78)
  - Wells, Fargo badge (Box 4., Folder 79)
  - Wells, Fargo stamps (Box 4., Folder 80)
  - Provisioning cars (Box 4., Folder 81)
  - Checks and receipts (Box 4., Folder 82)
  - Wells, Fargo tags (Box 4., Folder 83)
  - Proclamation of Mayor E. E. Schmitz to prevent looting. (Box 4., Folder 84)
  - N. Y., Central ad (Box 4., Folder 85)
  - Wells, Fargo day (Box 4., Folder 86)
  - Wells, Fargo semi-centennial (Box 4., Folder 87)
  - J. J. Valentine (Box 4., Folder 88)
  - Two periodical articles pertaining to the Confederate Navy. (Box 4., Folder 101)
- Photographs
  - Photographs of Wells, Fargo employees, men and women, stage coaches, sailing vessels, and related scenes. (Box 4., Folder 89-100)
- Henry Chester Ward
  - H.C. Ward letter-book, 1893-1895.Includes four stories in longhand about stage operations in California. (Box 4., Folder 102)
  - H.C. Ward diary, Nov. 17, 1869-Feb.9, 1870.Includes notes added at a later date. (Box 4., Folder 103)
  - Letters to H.C. Ward, 1879-1902. (Box 4., Folder 104)
  - H.C. Ward, last will & testament. (Box 4., Folder 105)
LISTING FOR OUT-GOING CORRESPONDENCE VOLUMES
The letters in these books are arranged chronologically on this list, not just according to page number. Unless otherwise noted, letters are from Bradford to the people named.
- H.B. Parsons, 7 Nov. 1888; 1 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 7 Nov. 1888; 2 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 8 Nov. 1888; 3 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 9 Nov. 1888; 4 (Volume 1)
- H. Wadsworth, 13 Nov. 1888; 5 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 14 Nov. 1888; 6 (Volume 1)
- Victor Richardson, 14 Nov. 1888; 7 (Volume 1)
- F. E. W. Bowen, 14 Nov. 1888; 8 (Volume 1)
- Charles Jennings, 14 Nov. 1888; 9 (Volume 1)
- W.J. Hancock, 20 Nov. 1888; 10 (Volume 1)
- Wm. Utz, 22 Nov. 1888; 11 (Volume 1)
- D. B. Horton, 22 Nov. 1888; 12 (Volume 1)
- Peter Wright and Sons, 22 Nov. 1888; 15-16 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 23 Nov. 1888; 13-14 (Volume 1)
- Virginia Seymour, 28 Nov. 1888; 17 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Dec. 1888; 47 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 5 Dec. 1888; 18-19 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 6? Dec. 1888; 20 (Volume 1)
- illegible, 6 Dec. 1888; 21 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. E. T. Gerry, 6 Dec. 1888; 22 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 18 Dec. 1888; 23-24 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 22 Dec. 1888; 22 (Volume 1)
- M.J. O'Brien, 22 Dec. l888; 26 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 24 Dec. 1888; 27-28 (Volume 1)
- Letters not by Bradford nor to Bradford concerning freight rates, n.d.; 29-38 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Jan. 1889; 42 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Jan. 1889; 43 (Volume 1)
- M.J. O'Brien, 2 Jan. 1889; 39 (Volume 1)
- W.T. Mengut, 3 Jan. 1889; 40 (Volume 1)
- G.W. Morse, 3 Jan. 1889; 41 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 4 Jan. 1889; 44 (Volume 1)
- E.T. Gerry, 4 Jan. 1889; 45-46 (Volume 1)
- Comment on Wells Fargo, n.d.; 48 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 4 Jan. 1889; 49-50 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 9 Jan. 1889; 51 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 14 Jan. 1889; 52 (Volume 1)
- Blank, n.d.; 53 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 28 Jan. 1889; 54 (Volume 1)
- Wm. Norton, 29 Jan. 1889; 55 (Volume 1)
- Removed from book, 56 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 7 Feb. 1889; 57 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 7 Feb. 1889; 58 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 7 Feb. 1889; 59 (Volume 1)
- Letter not by or to Bradford, n.d.; 60 (Volume 1)
- A. Lagugun, 19 Feb. 1889; 73-75 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 22 Feb. 1889; 61 (Volume 1)
- Letter not by or to Bradford, n.d.; 62 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Mar. 1889; 63 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Mar. 1889; 66 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Mar. 1889; 67 (Volume 1)
- F.J. Massey, 4 Mar. 1889; 64 (Volume 1)
- Letter not by or to Bradford, n.d.; 65 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 6 Mar. 1889; 68-69 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons Probably 6 March, -Mar. 1889; 70-71 (Volume 1)
- Letter not by or to Bradford, n.d.; 72 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 19 Mar. 1889; 76 (Volume 1)
- Distribution list, n.d.; 77 (Volume 1)
- Kinsey, 21 Mar. 1889; 78 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 22 Mar. 1889; 79-80 (Volume 1)
- M.J. O'Brien, 23 Mar. 1889; 81 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Crosby, 23 Mar. 1889; 82 (Volume 1)
- J.E. Nayark?, 25 Mar. 1889; 83 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Crosby, 26 Mar. 1889; 84-85 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 26 Mar. 1889; 86 (Volume 1)
- Letter not by or to Bradford, n.d.; 87-88 (Volume 1)
- E.A. Hawley, 29 Mar. 1889; 89 (Volume 1)
- Distribution list, n.d.; 90 (Volume 1)
- E.S. Pillsbury, 30 Mar. 1889; 91 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Apr. 1889; 92-93 (Volume 1)
- Anson Gorten, 1 Apr. 1889; 94 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine, 1 Apr. 1889; 95 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Apr. 1889; 96 (Volume 1)
- Wm. Pridham, 2 Apr. 1889; 94 (Volume 1)
- Humstone, 3 Apr. 1889; 97 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. Hix, 4 Apr. 1889; 98 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Crosby, 4 Apr. 1889; 99 (Volume 1)
- Fink, 4 Apr. 1889; 100 (Volume 1)
- E.J. Pillsbury, 15 Apr. 1889; 101 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Plant, 19 Apr. 1889; 102 (Volume 1)
- Hancock, 19 Apr. 1889; l02 (Volume 1)
- H.W. Titus, 25 Apr. 1889; 103-104 (Volume 1)
- List of names, n.d.; 105-06 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 25 Apr. 1889; 107 (Volume 1)
- E.J. Crowe, 26 Apr. 1889; 108 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. MacKay, 26 Apr. 1889; 109-110 (Volume 1)
- Miller, 26 Apr. 1889; 111 (Volume 1)
- Taylor, 26 Apr. 1889; 112 (Volume 1)
- W. Towle, 26 Apr. 1889; 113 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 26 Apr. 1999; 114 (Volume 1)
- Marshall, 27 Apr. 1839; 115 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 3 May 1889; 116-17 (Volume 1)
- Letter not by or to Bradford, n.d.; 118 (Volume 1)
- Miss Scoffy, 6 May 1889; 119 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. E.B. Comfort, 7 May 1889; 120 (Volume 1)
- M.J. O'Brien, 7 May 1889; 121 (Volume 1)
- Schiller Herford, 7 May 1889; 122 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 8 May 1889; 123 (Volume 1)
- this letter is illegible, May 1889; 124 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine practically illegible, May 1889; 125 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine, May 1889; 275 (Volume 1)
- List of cities, May 1889; 126 (Volume 1)
- W. Hutton, May 1889; 127 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. P.A. Hearst, May 1889; 128 (Volume 1)
- T.T. Morford, 1 June 1889; 129 (Volume 1)
- F.W. Sharon, 8 June 1889; 130-131 (Volume 1)
- B.A. Haggin, 8 June 1889; l32 (Volume 1)
- Miller, 8 June 1889; 133 (Volume 1)
- Miller, 8 June 1889; 134 (Volume 1)
- Kink or Fink, 8 June 1889; 135 (Volume 1)
- Hinley, 8 June 1889; 136 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 10 June 1889; 137 (Volume 1)
- Miller, 11 June 1889; 138 (Volume 1)
- Miller, 11 June 1889; 139 (Volume 1)
- Miller, 11 June 1889; 140 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 11 June 1889; 141 (Volume 1)
- W. Hutton, 17 June 1889; 142 (Volume 1)
- Thos. T. Morford, 18 June 1889; 143 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Land, 20 June 1889; 144 (Volume 1)
- M.J. O'Brien, 21 June 1889; 148 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine, 22 June 1889; 149 (Volume 1)
- W. Pridham, 22 June 1889; 150 (Volume 1)
- T.T. Morford, 22 June 1889; 151 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. Irwin, 24 June 1889; 155 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Land, 25 June 1889; 145 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 25 June 1889; 146 (Volume 1)
- T. Kinsey, 25 June 1889; 147 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 25 June 1889; 152 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Land, 25 June 1889; 153 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Land, 25 June 1889; 154 (Volume 1)
- Miller, 25 June 1889; 155 (Volume 1)
- Miller, 25 June 1889; 156 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Watkins, 25 June 1889; 157 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Watkins, 25 June 1889; 158 (Volume 1)
- M.M. Mitchell, 13 July 1889; 159 (Volume 1)
- Geo. Connor, 20 July 1889; 160-161 (Volume 1)
- Letter not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 162 (Volume 1)
- Gordon Blanding, 23 July 1889; 163 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Cameron, 23 July 1889; 164 (Volume 1)
- Capt. P.J. Irving, 23 July 1889; 165 (Volume 1)
- G. C. Nicholson, 29 July 1889; 166-67 (Volume 1)
- O.H. Taylor, 2 Aug. 1889; 168 (Volume 1)
- W. Kempson, 2 Aug. 1889; 169 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 2 Aug. 1889; 170 (Volume 1)
- L.S. White, 7 Aug. 1889; 171 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine, 13 Aug. 1889; 172 (Volume 1)
- J.W. Graham, 14 Aug. 1889; 173 (Volume 1)
- F.W. Sharon, 15 Aug. 1889; 174 (Volume 1)
- Crosby, Achamair & Van Givin?, 15 Aug. 1889; 175 (Volume 1)
- J.W. Graham, 16 Aug. 1889; 175 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 20 Aug. l889; 176 (Volume 1)
- J.B. Curtis, 20 Aug. l889.; 177 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Parsell, 20 Aug. l889; 178 (Volume 1)
- T. H. Ismay, 20 Aug. l889; 179 (Volume 1)
- Dr. O'Loughlin, 20 Aug. l889; 180 (Volume 1)
- Mr. Ditchfield, 20 Aug. l889; 181 (Volume 1)
- Mr. Taylor, 20 Aug. l889; 182 (Volume 1)
- Capt. F.L. Land, 20 Aug. l889; 183 (Volume 1)
- T. H. Ismay, 20 Aug. l889; 184 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine, 20 Aug. l889; 185 (Volume 1)
- J.R. Thayer, 21 Aug. l889; 186 (Volume 1)
- G. Blanding, 23 Aug. l889; 187-88 (Volume 1)
- A.A. Green, 30 Aug. l889; 189-90 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 2 Sept. 1889; 191-96 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 2 Sept. 1889; 197-201 (Volume 1)
- C. Reigensberg, 6 Sept. 1889; 202 (Volume 1)
- Letter not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 203 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 11 Sept. 1889; 204 (Volume 1)
- W.B. Files, 12 Sept. 1889; 205 (Volume 1)
- D.B. Norton, 13 Sept. 1889; 205 (Volume 1)
- F.E. Chadwick, 14 Sept. 1889; 206 (Volume 1)
- Dudley Evans, 14 Sept. 1889; 207-208 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 17 Sept. 1889; 209 (Volume 1)
- Mr. D. Evans, 17 Sept. 1889; 211 (Volume 1)
- Chas. D. Cushing, 18 Sept. 1889; 210 (Volume 1)
- Wana ck, 19 Sept. 1889; 212 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 213-15 (Volume 1)
- G. L. Connor, 21 Sept. 1889; 215 (Volume 1)
- Letter not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 216 (Volume 1)
- P. Wright & Sons, 23 Sept. 1889; 217 (Volume 1)
- Kate Forsyth, 24 Sept. 1889; 217 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 218-19 (Volume 1)
- Marshall Field, 28 Sept. 1889; 220 (Volume 1)
- Letter not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 221 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. J.W. Graydon, 28 Sept. 1889; 222 (Volume 1)
- Dixon Agent, 28 Sept. 1889; 223 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 30 Sept. 1889; 224, (Volume 1)
- M.B. Davis, 30 Sept. 1889; 225 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 225-26 (Volume 1)
- Mr. Miller, 2 Oct. 1899; 227 (Volume 1)
- Capt. Watkins, 2 Oct. 1899; 228 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. Anthony, 2 Oct. 1899; 229 (Volume 1)
- E.P. Waltham, 3 Oct. 1899; 230 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 3 Oct. 1899; 231 (Volume 1)
- C.H. Tilley, 4 Oct. 1899; 231a (Volume 1)
- H.B. Plant, 7 Oct. 1899; 232 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. D. Bixler, 7 Oct. 1899; 233 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 234 (Volume 1)
- G.E. Hancock, 10 Oct. 1899; 235 (Volume 1)
- Letter not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 235 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 12 Oct. 1899; 236-37 (Volume 1)
- D.B. Horton, 14 Oct. 1899; 238-40 (Volume 1)
- D.B. Horton, 15 Oct. 1899; 240 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 15 Oct. 1899; 241 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Plant, 15 Oct. 1899; 242 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 242-44 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 21 Oct. 1899; 245 (Volume 1)
- Wm. Nichols, Jr., 21 Oct. 1899; 246 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. Anthony, 22 Oct. 1899; 247 (Volume 1)
- E.S. Griffing, 30 Oct. 1899; 248 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 30 Oct. 1899; 248 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 249-50 (Volume 1)
- Capt. F. Watkins, 1 Nov. 1889; 251 (Volume 1)
- Stuart W. Miller, 1 Nov. 1889; 252 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. Hearst, 1 Nov. 1889; 253 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 254 (Volume 1)
- Mr. Norton, 5 Nov. 1889; 255 (Volume 1)
- Mr. Norton, 5 Nov. 1889; 256 (Volume 1)
- A.A. Green, 14 Nov. 1889; 257 (Volume 1)
- R.P. Lounsby, 14 Nov. 1889; 257 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 14 Nov. 1889; 258 (Volume 1)
- R.P. Hughes, 14 Nov. 1889; 258 (Volume 1)
- C.S. Ruggles, 14 Nov. 1889; 259 (Volume 1)
- H.H. Browning, 14 Nov. 1889; 260-61 (Volume 1)
- H.H. Browning, 14 Nov. 1889; 262-63 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. Hearst, 21 Nov. 1889; 264 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. A.E. Head, 25 Nov. 1889; 265 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Plant, 25 Nov. 1889; 266 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford;Expense Item, n.d.; 266-67 (Volume 1)
- F.W. Sharon, 27 Nov. 1889; 268 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. A.E. Head, 27 Nov. 1889; 268 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 269-70 (Volume 1)
- C.H. Gardiner, 9 Dec. 1889; 271 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 16 Dec. 1889; 276 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 16 Dec. 1889; 277-79 (Volume 1)
- Thomas Kinsey, 17 Dec. 1889; 271 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine, 17 Dec. 1889; 272 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. D. Bixler, 17 Dec. 1889; 273 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 273 (Volume 1)
- Blank, 274 (Volume 1)
- T.W. Robertson, 27 Dec. 1889; 280 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 7 Jan. 1890; 281 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 7 Jan. 1890; 282 (Volume 1)
- Geo. L. Connor, 8 Jan. 1890; 283 (Volume 1)
- G.E. Hancock, 22 Jan. 1890; 284 (Volume 1)
- M.H. Hickey, 29 Jan. 1890; 285 (Volume 1)
- Letters not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 286 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 31 Jan. 1890; 287 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 3 Feb. 1890; 288-90 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 3 Feb. 1890; 291-94 (Volume 1)
- E.M. Cooper, 3 Feb. 1890; 295 (Volume 1)
- H.J. Bullay, 6 Feb. 1890; 298 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 10 Feb. 1890; 299-300 (Volume 1)
- J. Connor, 12 Feb. 1890; 301 (Volume 1)
- Gen. Anson McCook, 20 Feb. 1890; 302 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 20 Feb. 1800; 303 (Volume 1)
- Mr. Prevost, 20 Feb. 1890; 304 (Volume 1)
- Letter not to nor by Bradford, 20 Feb. 1890; 305&9 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 25 Feb. 1890; 306-07 (Volume 1)
- A. Blum, 25 Feb. 1890; 308 (Volume 1)
- Orrin Peck, 26 Feb. 1890; 296-97 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 18 Mar. 1890; 310 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 18 Mar. 1890; 311-12 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 27 Mar. 1890; 313 (Volume 1)
- O.T. Taylor, 27 Mar. 1890; 313 (Volume 1)
- A.M. McBlair, 27 Mar. 1890; 314 (Volume 1)
- Letter not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 314 (Volume 1)
- Delafield, McGavain?, 1 Apr. 1890; 315 (Volume 1)
- C.F. Spotswood, 24 Apr. 1890; 316 (Volume 1)
- Capt. W. Mayo, 24 Apr. 1890; 317 (Volume 1)
- Capt. F.H. McCormick, 24 Apr. 1890; 318 (Volume 1)
- Gen. V.F. Croner, 25 Apr. 1890; 319 (Volume 1)
- Gen. V.F. Croner, 25 Apr. 1890; 320 (Volume 1)
- Evans--a fragment, 29 Apr. 1890; 321 (Volume 1)
- Christeson, 29 Apr. 1890; 321 (Volume 1)
- Dud1ey Evans, 29 Apr. 1890; 322 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 20 May 1890; 323 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 21 May 1890; 324 (Volume 1)
- W.R. Hearst, 23 May 1890; 325 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 26 May 1890; 326-27 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 26 May 1890; 328 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 2 June 1890; 329-30 (Volume 1)
- E.M. Cooper, 6 June 1890; 331 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 12 June 1890; 332-33 (Volume 1)
- M. Collins, 19 June 1890; 334 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 July 1890; 337 (Volume 1)
- A. Christeson, 2 July 1890; 338-40 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 10 July 1890; 341 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 14 July 1890; 342-43 (Volume 1)
- H.H. Browning, 22 July 1890; 344 (Volume 1)
- R.W. Farnham, 22 July 1890; 345 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine, 23 July 1890; 346 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 1 Aug. 1890; 347 (Volume 1)
- John Muller, 5 Aug. 1890; 348 (Volume 1)
- A.M. McBlair, 6 Aug. 1890; 350 (Volume 1)
- H.H. Browning, 7 Aug. 1890; 349 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 14 Aug. 1890; 351 (Volume 1)
- Mrs. Homer, 19 Aug. 1890; 352 (Volume 1)
- Alfred Kempson, 25 Aug. 1890; 353 (Volume 1)
- Z.B. Haggin, 25 Aug. 1890; 353 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 28 Aug. 1890; 354 (Volume 1)
- Letter not to nor by Bradford, n.d.; 355 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 11 Sept. 1890; 356-57 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 11 Sept. 1890; 358-59 (Volume 1)
- Geo. L. Connor, 13 Sept. 1890; 360 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 16 Sept. 1890; 361-62 (Volume 1)
- Morris Euro. Express Co., 17 Sept. 1890; 363 (Volume 1)
- Morris Euro. Express Co., 17 Sept. 1890; 364 (Volume 1)
- Geo. L. Connor, 17 Sept. 1890; 365 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 17 Sept. 1890; 366-67 (Volume 1)
- Geo. L. Connor, 23 Sept. 1890; 368 (Volume 1)
- Morris Euro. Express Co., 25 Sept. 1890; 369 (Volume 1)
- R.H.W. Dwight, 10 Oct. 1890; 370 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 15 Oct. 1890; 371-73 (Volume 1)
- J.J. Valentine, 18 Oct. 1890; 373 (Volume 1)
- A.M. McBlair, 20 Oct. 1890; 374 (Volume 1)
- Dudley Evans, 21 Oct. 1890; 374 (Volume 1)
- Letter not by nor to Bradford, n.d.; 375 (Volume 1)
- Benj. F. Tracy, 31 Oct. 1890; 376 (Volume 1)
- Paymaster Gen. U. S. Navy, 31 Oct. 1890; 376 (Volume 1)
- Morris Euro. Express Co., 3 Nov. 1890; 377 1 (Volume 1)
- Letter not by nor to Bradford, n.d.; 378 (Volume 1)
- P or J. Bra da and Anson Gorton, 4 Nov. 1890; 379 (Volume 1)
- E.J. Crowe, 10 Nov. 1890; 380 (Volume 1)
- Mr. Crowe, 10 Nov. 1890; 381-82 (Volume 1)
- Gen. B.F. Tracy, 12 Nov. 1890; 383 (Volume 1)
- Edward May, 12 Nov. 1890; 384 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 13 Nov. 1890; 385-86 (Volume 1)
- Eaves and Aller, n.d.; 387-88 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 18 Nov. 1890; 389 (Volume 1)
- W.H. Crocker, 21 Nov. 1890; 390 (Volume 1)
- C.P. Curtis, Jr., 1 Dec. 1890; 391 (Volume 1)
- W.H. Crocker, 1 Dec. 1890; 392 (Volume 1)
- Lloyd Tevis, 15 Dec. 1890; 393 (Volume 1)
- W.R. Hearst, 15 Dec. 1890; 394 (Volume 1)
- E.A. Rix, 15 Dec. 1890; 395 (Volume 1)
- Sir Sidney Waterlow, 19 Dec. 1890; 396 (Volume 1)
- Robinson & Allen, 19 Dec. 1890; 396a (Volume 1)
- Sir Sidney Waterlow, 23 Dec. 1890; 397 (Volume 1)
- Robinson & Allen, 23 Dec. 1890; 398 (Volume 1)
- Mr. O'Brien, 17 Jan. 1891; 400 (Volume 1)
- H.B. Parsons, 21 Jan. 1891; 401-02 (Volume 1)